yourwebapps.com 2015-04-07

# YourWebApps.com Privacy Policy

YourWebApps.com recognizes that its customers need to know YourWebApps.com will respect and protect the privacy of information placed in a YourWebApps.com WebApp or GroupApp. This document describes how YourWebApps.com safeguards your privacy and treats personal information. We understand that for you to take full advantage of the benefits of this interactive medium, we must do what we can to ensure that your privacy is secure.

**1\. We do not disclose the information placed in your WebApp or GroupApp.**

YourWebApps.com honors the confidentiality of its customers' private information placed in a WebApp or GroupApp. We are required by law to disclose information under certain, limited, circumstances, and you should keep this in mind when posting information to your WebApp or GroupApp.

> a) YourWebApps.com reserves the right to reveal data in cooperation with a request or investigation by any governmental body or governmental agency, or in response to a subpoena issued by any governmental body or governmental agency;
> 
> b) YourWebApps.com reserves the right to examine any data in the course of responding to any claim by a third party that a Customer or Visitor is using a WebApp or GroupApp in connection with an infringing, illegal or improper activity or that the data infringes rights of the third party.
> 
> c) YourWebApps.com reserves the right to disclose the identity of a Customer, or information allowing identification of a Customer, in response to request for identification in connection with claim of Copyright or Trademark infringement by the Customer.
> 
> d) Information posted or uploaded by Customers may be stored on computers maintained by and in control of YourWebApps.com's Service Provider. Any expectation of privacy by a Customer is limited by and subject to the scope of the Service Provider's privacy policy

**2\. We do not sell your registration information (name, telephone number, mailing address, credit card information, etc.) unless you specifically authorize us to do so.**

We have three exceptions to this policy. We will release specific information about your account to law enforcement authorities if compelled to by legal process. We will provide identification information in response to a request for identification in connection with a claim of Copyright or Trademark infringement by a Customer. We may from time to time share aggregate registration information (such as total number of users who are free trial, active, trial over, etc.) with our partners (whom are under confidentiality obligations). However, since we make no commitments on behalf of our partners, we do encourage you to acquaint yourself with their individual privacy policies as well.

**3\. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access in order to safeguard your personal information.**

We use industry-standard technology to keep your personal information and your billing and account information as secure as possible. We also have put in place privacy protection control systems designed to ensure that your personal data remain safe and private.

Every Server Company employee is obligated to abide by the YourWebApps.com privacy policy. Employees who violate our privacy policies are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

Only authorized Server Company employees servicing YourWebApps.com, and employees of our Service Provider, are permitted to have access to your personal information and such access is limited by need.

We encourage our partners to clearly post their own privacy policies. Be sure to review their privacy policies and contact them directly if you have any questions.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Our third-party advertising companies also separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements for this site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

If you'd like to comment on or have questions about our privacy policy, have a concern or policy violation you wish to report, or wish to change or delete the customer information you submitted to YourWebApps.com, please contact Customer Support at support@yourwebapps.com or by calling (617) 249-0756.

Copyright © The Server Company. All Rights Reserved.
